命運如鑄劍之人 提前鍛造萬物 by- 埃斯庫羅斯
人類帝國
她回來了 她終於回到家了
She's back! She's home!
菲利帕回家了
Philippa came home!
兩年過去了
YOUNG GEORGIOU: Two years,
一切都和記憶中一模一樣
αnd everything looks exactly as I remember.
我以為再也見不到這里了
I never thought I would see this place again.
這一次我們有18個人
There were 18 of us this time.
從帝國各個角落被選中
Culled from every corner of the Empire
帶到地球參加比試
αnd brought to Terra for the contest.
他們說只有一個人能活到最後
We were told that only one of us would survive
熬過這些年
the years to come.
一個孩子…
One child.
…最純粹的帝國血脈
...the purest expression of the Terran identity.
他們讓我們自相殘殺
They pitted us against each other.
一個月又一個月 我們的人數不斷減少
And month by month, our numbers dwindled.
你...你贏了嗎
FATHER: Did...did you win?
結束了嗎
ls it over?
還剩下兩個人
Two of us still live.
桑和我
San and me.
我和桑
Me and San.
我們是二人
BOTH: We are two...
…卻如一人
...but one.
永遠如此
BOTH: Forever.
比試期間”朋友”這個詞是被禁止的
The word "friend" was forbidden during the contest,
但無人時我們會悄悄對彼此說出這個詞
but we whispered it to each other when no one could hear.
桑和我聯手對抗
San and I combined our skills
總督和其他參賽者
αgainst the proctor and the other contestants.
但只能有一個人成為皇帝
But only one of you could be emperor.
還剩最後一個任務
One task remains.
誰先完成誰就能統治帝國
The first to complete it rules the Empire,
另一個人余生都將
and the other spends the rest of their life
侍奉新皇帝
in servitude to the new emperor.
你們要做什麼
What do you have to do?
對不起
I'm sorry.
你做了什麼
What did you do? !
”不允許與過去有任何牽絆
”No ties to the old life are permitted.
皇帝只能忠於職責
”An emperor can only be loyal to duty.
帝國因此而強大
"Thus does the Empire remain strong.
帝國因此而強盛”
Thus does it grow. "
-媽媽 -菲利帕
Mom. Philippa.
你成功了 而你的對手失敗了
You succeeded where your competitor could not.
把他帶上來
Bring him here.
桑沒有力量通過最後的考驗
San did not have the strength to pass the final test.
此刻他的村莊正在燃燒 昭示著他的懦弱
Even now, his village burns as a testament to his cowardice.
我愛你
: llove you.
你贏了這場較量
TERRAN PROCTOR: You have won the contest.
來領取你的勝利吧
Claim your victory.
桑 上前來
San, step forward.
你如今只為臣服於她而活
You live now only to serve at her heel.
跪拜吧 向掌控你生命的人
Kneel before the one who owns your life.
我們本為二者…
: We are two...
卻合為一體
But one.
但這一切已經結束了
Not anymore.
向喬治歐陛下致敬
TERRAN PROCTOR: AII hail Philippa Georgiou!
向帝王致敬
AlI hail the emperor!
致敬 致敬 致敬
CROWD: Hail! Hail! Hail!
致敬
Hail!
這里是指揮部
CONTROL: This is Control
向阿爾法小隊隊長發送優先級消息
with a priority message for Alpha Team Leader.
你的目標是菲利帕·喬治歐
Your subject is Emperor Philippa Georgiou,
特倫帝國的前任統治者
former ruler of the Terran Empire.
她來自一個平行宇宙
lt's in a parallel universe
那里的罪犯數量之多
with the most criminal population
史無前例
in recorded history.
即便在那里 喬治歐的暴行也是最令人發指的
Even there, Georgiou had the market cornered on atrocities.
2257年 她被帶到我們的宇宙
ln 2257, she was brought to our universe
加入了31區
αnd joined Section 31,
但幾年後我們失去了聯系
but after a few years, we lost contact.
最近 喬治歐用假身份出現
Recently, Georgiou was spotted using an alias
在聯邦空間外的邊境地帶
in the border territory outside Federation space,
我們正在那里追蹤黑市上的一個新威脅
where we're tracking a new threat on the black market.
這就是你們小隊的任務
This is where your team comes in.
聯邦條約禁止我們越過那條邊境線
Federation treaty forbids us from crossing over that border,
這意味著星際艦隊不能直接插手
which means Starfleet cannot get its hands dirty.
你和你的31區小隊將潛入 與喬治歐取得聯系
You and your 31 team will go in, make contact with Georgiou
幫助識別並消除這個威脅
to help identify and neutralize the threat.
但要記住…
But make no mistqke...
這條惡犬會咬人 小心你們的後背
this dog bites, so watch your backs.
你們有24小時完成任務
You have 24 hours to complete the mission.
開始行動吧
Get to work.
星際述肌: 31區
ed3000翻譯官 譯
星歷1292. 4
杜弗朗克夫人
VIRGIL: Madame du Franc?
蜜月套房發生了點小意外
Small incident in the honeymoon suite.
恐怕那位新娘在關鍵時刻
I'm afraid the bride molted
蛻皮了
just as things were coming to a climax.
維吉爾 說重點
GEORGIOU: Virgil, get to the point. -
我已派生化危機小組前去 並轉達了您的慰問
I sent a biohazard team and your condolences.
另外 有位客人希望能與您談談
Also, there's a customer hoping for α word with you.
他看起來很清醒 但卻令人著迷
He seems entirely sober but quite intoxicating.
杜弗朗克夫人願意見您
Mqdame Veronique du Franc will see you.
阿洛克·薩哈爾 見過杜弗朗克夫人
Alok Sahar, Madame Veronique du Franc.
杜弗朗克夫人通常需要預約才見客
Madame du Franc normally does business by appointment.
我想預約
I'd like to make an oppointment.
哦 這位先生想預約呢
Oh, the gentleman would like to make an appointment.
現在 現在 夫人
ALOK: Now. VIRGIL: Now, madame.
不可能 不可能
: lmpossible. : lmpossible.
嗯
GEORGIOU: Mmm.
Mmm.
再見 維吉爾
Au revoir, Virgil.
嗯哼
Mm- hmm.
這是違法的
ALOK: That is illegal.
而這能賺錢
And that makes money.
這是家正經場所
GEORGIOU: This is a reputable establishment.
我聽說不是
ALOK: Not what I heard.
不如去你辦公室談談 嗯？
- Why don't we discuss it in your office? - Hmm.
我為什麼要帶你去我的辦公室 阿洛克·薩哈爾？
Why would I take you to my office, Alok Sahar?
因為這需要親身體驗
Because it's α hands- on experience.
甜薊花
ALOK: Dulcet thistle.
甜薊花已經滅絕了
Dulcet thistle's extinct.
我有十二公斤這玩意
I've got α dozen keys of this stuff.
要來點嗎？
Have you partaken?
這會是我少有的第一次體驗之一
This would be one of my few first times.
勁很大
Packs a punch.
讓人愉悅的那種
- Ahappy punch. Mmm.
幹杯
Bottoms up.
為金錢 為你
- To money. To you.
嗯
GEORGIOU: Mmm.
現在 別裝了
Now, let's cut the shit.
31區來我的空間站做什麼?
What is Section 31 doing in my space station?
嗯？以為我認不出特工嗎？
Hmm? You think I don't know an agent when I see one?
你帶著六名特工
You're heading up a team of six operatives,
他們都在酒吧里
αnd they're dll over the bar.
那邊那個變形者
There's the Chameloid,
綠血的變種人
α green- blooded shape- shifter,
正試圖勾引一個德爾塔人
trying to muster sexy time with a Deltan,
一個活生生的誘餌
a walking honey trap
31區顯然在用她轉移注意力
31's obviously using αs a distraction.
但變形者是銀河系唯一
Except Chameloids are the only species in the galaxy
對德爾塔人魅力免疫的種族
immune to Deltan sexy time charm.
還有那邊那個全身高科技裝備的家夥
Then there's the guy with all the high- end mech,
站在後面一副若有所思的樣子
standing in the back, looking like he has thoughts.
機械生命不只是靠蠻力
Mech life, it ain't just about the brute force.
我猜 武器很重 智商很輕
GEORGIOU: I'mgonna say heavy on artillery, low on IQ.
真遺憾
I'm so sorry.
別忘了那個瓦肯人
And we can't forget the Vulcan,
笑得比台上的笑話還誇張
laughing way too hard at the stage banter.
瓦肯人從不笑所以他要麼也是個蠢貨
And since Vulcans never laugh, he's either an idiot, too,
要麼是龐法導致精神失常
or lost his mind during pon farr and went insane.
得了吧 這很好笑
Oh, come on. That was funny.
還有你安排的那個一本正經的人類…
GEORGIOU: And the very serious human you stuck him with.
收斂點吧
Reel it in anytime.
她屁股里的棍子插得太深了
...she's got a stick so far up her backside,
都從嘴里冒出來了
it's coming out her mouth.
收斂點
Just reel it in.
那是
ALOK: That would be
加勒特中尉
Lieutenant Garrett. - Mmm.
星際艦隊
Starfleet.
歡樂的終結者
Where fun goes to die.
你們找到我花了夠久的
It took you long enough to find me.
我們知道你在巴拉姆
We knew that having you here on the Baraam
總有一天會對我們有用
would be valuable to us one day.
我現在可沒什麼動力
Well, I'm not feeling motivated to be valuable
為別人效力
to anyone but myself.
那麼 我們是不是該開始談條件了？
So, is this where we start negotiating?
嗯 那要看情況
Hmm, that depends.
你知道我多久了
How long have you known about me?
從你接手前任店主開始
Ever since you took over from the previous owner,
那人至今下落不明
who we still haven't found.
聽著
Well, all of.
-不是我幹的 -皇帝
That wasn't me. Emperor Georgiou,
我被授權逮捕你
I am authorized to arrest you
並抹除你的記憶
and wipe your mind clean. -
但我內心有個聲音
But then again, there's a part of me
想讓你繼續帶著這些記憶活著
that wants you to live with your memories.
那些大屠殺的記憶
The genocidal ones.
你有權逮捕我
Being authorized to arrest me
不代表你有能力逮捕我
isn't the same as being able to arrest me.
你真想讓31區 讓我
You really want Section 31 want me- -
一直追著你不放嗎
dogging you until the end of time?
無聊
: Boring.
過去總會追上你
The past always catches up with you.
不管你我是否承認
And as much as both of us
我這是在幫你
might hate it, I'm doing you α favor.
最後一個任務
One lqst mission.
聽著
Listen.
你相信命運嗎
Do you believe in fate?
我相信
Becouse I do.
你逃不過命運
You can't hide from it.
你在這里什麼都不是 喬治歐
You're nothing here, Georgiou.
我給你機會重返戰場
I'm giving you α chance to get back in.
參與銀河系級別的行動
In on the action on a galactic scale.
別再逃避了
Stop running from it.
做回真正的自己
Be who you are.
或者繼續在這當一輩子酒保
Or stay and tend bar for eternity.
開始吧
Let's get on with it.
菲利帕·喬治歐 來見見我的團隊
ALOK: Philippα Georgiou, meet my team.
這是梅勒
This is Melle.
澤夫
Zeph.
你像個瑞士軍刀
You look like a Swiss Army knife.
等等
Uh, hold on.
我不知道那是什麼 但我不會
I don't know what that means, but I'm not gonna
站在這被侮辱
just stand here and get insulted.
我說的不是你
I'm not talking about you.
說的是你的戰甲
I'm talking αbout your suit.
你是新來的
ZEPH: Um, you're new,
我就說這一次
so I'm gonna just explain this one time
當你說起戰甲的時候
that when you are talking about the suit,
就是在說澤夫本人
you're talking about Zeph.
-噢 -澤夫患有
- Oh. QUASI: Zeph suffers from
所謂的機甲畸形癥
what we call mecha dysmorphia.
雖然我不知道那是什麼
ZEPH: And I may not know what that is,
但我也不會接受
but I'm also not gonna take that
你這麼說 誇西 我很生氣
from you, Quas, and personally I'm offended.
-你得知道... -這是事實
- I think you should know...- Well, it's accurate.
這不是診斷結果 你又不是醫生
It's not α diagnosis. You're not α doctor.
澤夫 澤夫 澤夫
ALOK: Zeph. Zeph, Zeph!
-他知道 他都知道 -好吧
- He knows. He knows. He knows. - Okay, fine.
他知道
He knows.
-他明白 他明白 -是的
He gets it. He gets it. Yes.
那個瓦肯人呢
Okay, what obout that Vulcan?
沒人告訴她嗎
Nobody told her?
這個 你說的這個
This? The thing you're talking to?
瓦肯人只是台機器
The Vulcan's just a machine.
我在里面
I'm inside.
操控著它
Driving.
我從後備載具里控制這具身體
I control the body from a backup vehicle.
用它進入一些狹小空間
Yeah, something I use to get into tight spots.
嗨你好
Hi there.
我是弗茲
I'm Fuzz.
弗茲是納米族
Fuzz is a Nanokin.
很有趣的家夥
Real fun- loving guy.
你好
Hello.
除了他發起瘋來的時候
Except for when he's not.
那時他就失控 有暴力傾向
Then he's deranged with an anger management problem.
你說第一點就夠了 誇西
Well, you could've stopped αt the first thing, Quasi.
盜版瓦肯載具
A bootleg Vulcan conveyance?
黑市上一定有不少好東西
You must see cool stuff on the black market.
納米族都愛撿破爛
QUASI: Nanokins are pretty scavengery.
31區第一次接觸他們
31 made first contact when
是在一艘廢棄飛船上發現了他們的寄生
we discovered an infestation on a derelict ship.
-誇西 -糟了
Quasi. Oh, shit.
再說一遍寄生 誇西
: Say"infestαtion"one more time, Quasi.
說啊 叫我撿破爛的 你這團黑灰
Soy"scavenger, "you sack of amorphous soot!
我...說完我就後悔了
l- ls- - I heard it as soon as I said it.
我要揍你
I will kick your ass
揍到你連個形狀都凝聚不了
until you cannot form a solid mass of...
弗茲 弗茲 冷靜
Fuzz. Fuzz. Lock it down.
我很冷靜
I am locked down.
我被困在這個巨大的機器瓦肯頭里
I'm trapped inside α giant robot Vulcan head.
還有誰比我更冷靜
No one is more locked down than me right now!
納米族的情緒波動很奇怪
Nanokins have o wonky emotional spectrum.
不不不不不不 我不會
No, no, no, no, no, no, Iwillnot
接受你的輕視 梅勒
be condescended to, Melle,
尤其是你 說實話…
particularly not by you, because honest.
我愛你 你太完美了
MELLE: Ilove you. You are everything.
-我這情緒你喜歡嗎 -弗茲
Does my spectrum work for you? - ZEPH: Fuzz.
-就是說 你覺得如何… -弗茲
- Imean, like, like, are you into it or...- Fuzz!
弗茲
Fuzz!
她在羞辱你 夥計
She's insulting you, pal.
我知道德爾塔人就這德行
I know Deltans are gonna do their Deltan thing,
但你也該有點自尊吧
but have a little self- respect, would you?
我們繼續嗎
Can we continue?
這位是瑞秋·加勒特中尉
And that's Lieutenant Rachel Gorrett.
她只為這次任務臨時加入31區
She is detailed to Section 31 for this one mission only.
你得罪了誰才來黑ops的 中尉
Who did you piss off to get stuck in black ops, Lieutenant?
星際艦隊是來確保我們守規矩的
Starfleet is here to make sure we color inside the lines.
星際艦隊是來保衛聯邦
GARRETT: Starfleet is here to defend the Federation,
維護和平 防止謀殺發生的
keep the peace and make sure no one commits murder.
-那你呢 -等一下
·And you? - One moment.
誇西進入我的視野
ALOK: Quasi came on my radar
是因為他證實了神經簇的存在
when he proved the existence of glioclusters.
神經簇只是理論上存在
Glioclusters are theoretical.
曾經是理論上存在
Formerly theoretical.
生命就是無數分支的可能性
Life is just branching possibilities.
你知道它們會以你想象不到的方式綻放
You know, they bloom and blossom any way you can imagine.
比如說 我現在可能會被你嚇到
For example, I could be intimidated by you right now.
畢竟 你殺過
I mean, after all, you've murdered
那麼多人…
so many people.
而你似乎正在洞穿我的靈魂
and you seem to be staring right into my soul.
我可以對此做出回應
I could respond to that
或者我可以觀察當下的感受
or I could observe my feelings right now,
把它鎖起來 專注於該做的事
lock it away and do what I need to do.
或者…誇斯 選一個吧
- Or...- Quas. Pick one. Hmm?
好的 有時誇斯會看到
QUASI: Yes. - MELLE: Sometimes Quasi sees
太多選擇而大腦當機 謝謝你 梅勒
so many options he gets brain- freeze. - Thank you, Melle.
誇斯 我們繼續好嗎 嗯
- Quasi, can we carryon, please? - Mm- hmm.
我們的目標是達達·諾伊
Our target's name is Dqda Noe.
道德觀念成問題
Dubious moral compass.
他曾在瓦特殖民地經營一家病理實驗室 後來叛逃了
Ran α pathology lab on the Watt Colonies before he went rogue.
從那以後 他一直在按需設計生物武器
Since then, he's been designing bioweapons on spec.
諾伊正在前往巴拉姆 準備把他最新的作品
Noe's on his way to the Baraam to sell his latest creation
賣給米諾斯最高議會
to the Minosian High Council.
雖然我們與米諾斯勢力沒有正式敵對
There are no formal hostilities with the Minosian Sway,
但如果他們得到這種
but that could change if they get their hands
超級武器 情況就會改變
on a superweapon.
我們知道這種生物超級武器是什麼嗎
GEORGIOU: Dowe know what this bio superweapon is?
不知道 但既然是達達·諾伊在賣 肯定很糟
GARRETT: No, but if Dada Noe is selling it, it's bad.
所以你們要確保這筆交易不會發生
So you're here to make sure the sale never happens.
怎麼做
How?
雖然你發現我們時計劃出了差錯
Things went south when you spotted us,
但計劃依然可行
but the plan is still solid.
首先 阿洛克要...
First, Alok was going to...
你可以說出來
You can soy it.
搭訕
Connect.
你
With you. -
歡迎光臨 嗯
Welcome! Mmm. Yes.
多可愛的想法
What o cute idea.
趁你被分散注意力時
Once we had you suitably distracted,
誇斯就能做他擅長的另一件事
Quasi would do the other thing Quasi does.
好了 誇斯
ALOK: Okay, Quasi.
請開始吧 當然
- If you would do the honors. Absolutely.
讓我們開工吧
Let's get to work.
歡迎 達達·諾伊
Welcome, Dada Noe.
這就到了弗茲登場的時候
ALOK: This is where Fuzz comes in.
你不會相信我能鉆進多小的地方
FUZZ: You wouldn't believe the tiny spots I can get into.
比如 體型改造裝置的內部結構
For example, the inner workings of body modifications.
一旦我飛進達達的體型改造裝置
Oh, once I fly inside Dada's body mod,
就該大顯身手了
well, then it's time to get to work.
那麼多電路
So many circuits.
那麼多可能出錯的地方
So many things that could go wrong.
這位能力至上主義者會指導我
Competency crusader here will talk me through
植入物的技術細節
the tech on the implant.
如果我覺得改動那個植入物會
And if I think we're putting Dada Noe's life in danger
危及達達·諾伊的生命
by tinkering with that implant,
我就會讓星際艦隊全面介入
I will unleash the full weight of Starfleet
這次行動
on this whole operotion.
拜托 我們說的可是個把超級武器賣給
Oy, we're talking about a bloke who's selling superweapons
任何有拉錫姆卡的三流恐怖分子的家夥
to any third- rate terrorist with a Lotinum card.
聽好了 廢品佬
GARRETT: Listen carefully, Junkyard.
星際艦隊不做暗殺
Starfleet does not do assassinotions.
得了 別把你的主要指令搞得一團亂
Ay, don't get your prime directives in α bunch.
你不會弄臟自己的手
You are not going to get your hands dirty
破壞自己成為艦長的機會
αnd mess up your chances of becoming captain.
我可是頂尖的科學官
I'm αtop- tier science officer.
蠻橫的家夥 死板鬼
Butt pretzel. - : Tight- ass.
真沒禮貌
So disrespectful.
等加勒特和弗茲切斷那個連接…
Soon as Garrett and Fuzz sever that link.
他就會被我們控制 我會在澤夫的幫助下
...he'll be under our control, and I'll take him down
制服他 嗯
with the help of Zeph. - Mm.
這才叫打擊 一個
That's what I callαhit. - One.
在買家到達巴拉姆之前
Dada Noe and his pathogen will be in custody
達達·諾伊和他的病原體就會被捕
before the buyers cqn even show up to the Baraam.
我們進去又出來
And we are in nd out.
嗯 不過…
Mm. Meh.
不過
OTHERS: Meh?
我有個更簡單的主意
I have o simpler idea.
歡迎 諾伊先生
Welcome, Monsieur Dada Noe.
很榮幸您光臨巴拉姆
We're honored to have you here at the Bqraam.
我是維羅妮克·杜弗朗克 這里的主人
I am Veronique du Franc, the proprietor.
我說過要準備好我的套房
I told them to have my suite ready.
當然 先生
Mais oui, monsieur.
讓我帶您去房間
May lescort you to your quarters?
來吧
Come.
我們有最精致的…
We have the most exquisite
我不敢相信你會相信這個反社會者
I can't believe you're trusting this sociopath.
好吧 中尉
ALOK: Well, Lieutenant,
你得做該做的事
you got to do what you got to do,
而我對反社會者還挺熟悉的
αnd l'm kind of familiar with sociopaths.
我說過不要帶我來
I said don't bring me.
希望您一路順風 先生
I trust your trip was without incident, monsieur.
你們的人確實把一切都安排得很妥當
Well, your people made everything easy.
這是我們的榮幸 到了
Our pleasure. Here we are.
真俗氣
So tacky.
不過這就是你的風格
But I guess that's what you're known for.
這是什麼
What's this?
這叫相位艙
It's called α phase pod.
我的一個客戶送給我的
A client of mine gave it to me as a gift,
我也給自己弄了一個
αnd I got one for myself, too.
你在幹什麼
What are you doing?
宇宙中的一切都以
Everything in the universe vibrates
特定的波長振動
- on αcertain wavelength. -
該死
Damn it.
把箱子還給我
Give me back my case.
不
No.
這要從你的安全押金里扣除
That's coming out of your security deposit.
相位艙會改變
The phase pod changes the wavelength
它們接觸物體的波長
of whatever they touch.
我與你相位不同 你也與我相位不同
I am out of phase with you, and you're out of phase with me.
但我與你的箱子相位相同
Iαm, however, in phase with your case.
我要把它帶走
And I will be taking it with me.
你不知道你惹上了什麼麻煩
You have no idea what you've started.
糟糕了
Whoopsie.
令人印象深刻
lmpressive.
你確定你是人類嗎
Are you sure you're human?
大多數時候是
Most days.
謝謝
Thank you.
把箱子給我
Give me the case.
你是誰
Who are you?
他往那邊跑了 那邊 那邊 那邊 那邊
He went that way. That way, that woy, that way, that way!
天啊 是外星人
Oh, aliens.
-赤身裸體的外星人 -快追 澤夫
- Nαked αliens. - ALOK: Go, Zeph, go.
他朝休息室去了 天哪 他們跑得真快
He's headed to the lounge. Man, they're moving fast.
梅勒 他朝你那邊去了
: Melle, he's coming to you.
天啊
Yikes.
沒事
No, it's okoy.
-我沒事 -梅勒 抓到他了嗎
- l'm all right. - Melle, you got him?
抓到了
Got him.
哇喔
Ooh- la- la!
天啊
Ay, amor.
這不可能
That's not possible.
我明明銷毀了它
I had that destroyed.
不 不
No. No!
這不可能
lt's not possible.
你認識那件武器
ALOK: You knew that weapon.
那是什麼
What is it?
好吧 那就來硬的
Fine. The hard way.
永恒祈求者請求覲見
MAN: The Eternal Supplicant begs opproach.
準予覲見
You have my permission.
至高無上的陛下
AlI hail Her Most Imperial Majesty,
祖國之母
Mother of the Fatherland,
-火山星的統治者 -什麼事
Overlord of Vulc- What is it?
已經完成了 陛下
lt is finished, Your Majesty.
我的工程師們呢
Where are my engineers?
他們…完工後就自盡了
: They...they took their own lives upon completion.
桑 你為誰而哭
Who is the tear for, San?
說
Speak.
為您而哭 陛下
lt is for you, Majesty.
這一切都是…
lt is oll
為了您
for you.
我問你 桑
I αsked you α question, San.
你為何為我哭泣
Why do you cry for me?
看著我
Look ot me.
你還記得我們是誰嗎
Do you remember who we were?
在這一切之前
Before oll this.
那個求知若渴的男孩
The curious boy.
那個天真無邪的女孩
The innocent girl.
我只記得我的失敗 陛下
I only remember my failure, Majesty.
別對我撒謊
Don't lie to me.
只有我們能理解
We were the only ones who could understand
活下去需要付出的代價
the cost to stay alive.
我們是一個團隊
We made o team.
我們互相需要 不是嗎
We needed each other, didn't we?
為了一起活下去
What did we say to carry each other through,
我們說過什麼
to survive together?
我們是二…
We are two.
為一體
SAN: But one.
我們是二為一體
BOTH: We are two but one.
如果那時我說
If I said then,
”讓我們逃走吧
"Let's run away,
逃離這場競爭
"let's flee this competition
逃離一切束縛我們的地球”
and everything that binds us to Terra, "
你會說什麼
what would you have said?
嗯
Hmm?
您這個問題的時機比您想象的更富詩意
The timing of your question is more poetic than you know.
那時的我會說好
I would have said yes.
那時
Then.
但現在呢
But now?
您本可以締造一個美好的統治
You could have made something beautiful with your reign.
但您卻選擇建造這個
lnstead, you chose to build this.
這意味著我認識的那個
That means that innocent girl I knew,
天真無邪的女孩
she hqs been...
已經…死了
: ...murdered.
這是什麼
What is this?
你…
You......
你也服了同樣的毒
You took the same poison?
不 我不允許你死
No! I forbid you to die!
沒有人願意活在
No one wants to live
您的世界里 皇帝陛下
in your world, Emperor.
您是個暴君
You ore a monster!
這又是什麼好地方
GEORGIOU: And what delightful place is this?
安全屋
ALOK: A safe house.
但對你來說可能不太安全
But maybe not so safe for you.
你是31區的人
You are Section 31.
為什麼不用刑逼我說出答案
Why aren't you torturing answers out of me?
你是個暴君
You're a tyrant.
真正的暴君
A real one.
刑訊對你沒用
Torture wouldn't work.
你為什麼如此了解像我這樣的人
How do you know so much about people like me?
嗯
Hmm?
你也曾經歷過暴政 而且記憶深刻
You learned tyranny somewhere, and you learned hard.
如果你要隱藏這點 就是軟弱
If you have to hide it, that's a weakness.
而我的搭檔不能軟弱
And I can't have thot in o partner.
-我們不是搭檔 -不是嗎
- We're not partners. - No?
我幫了很大忙
I've been very helpful.
你的計劃本行不通
You had a plan that couldn't work.
我給了你更好的方案
I gave you α better one.
讓你嘗到了行動的滋味
You gave me a tqste of the action,
知道你會想要更多
knowing I'd want more.
你需要我
You need me.
你選擇了我
You chose me.
為什麼
Why?
不管你以為你的任務是什麼
Whatever you believed your mission was,
情況比你想象的更糟
it's worse than you thought.
數十億人命危在旦夕 時間緊迫
Blllions of lives are at stake, and time is short.
你說你的故事 我就說我的
Tell me you, and I will tell you me.
這件事要成功 我必須
The only way this works is if I know
完全了解我在和誰打交道
exactly who I'm dealing with.
我也不是這個時代的人
I'm not from this time, either.
我生於20世紀的地球
I was born on Earth, 20th century.
你有350歲了
You are 350 years old?
差不多吧
More or less.
我沈睡了大部分時間
I slept most of that time.
在我被流放後
After my exile.
優生戰爭時期
The Eugenics Wars.
強化人…
Augments.
奪走了我的星球
took my planet.
我的家園
My home.
當時我們只有十來個人在戰鬥
There was maybe ten of us who fought.
我認識的人要麼中彈要麼被砍死
Everyone I knew either took a bullet or a blade.
但我也殺了不少敵人
But I gave some back.
她注意到了我
She noticed me.
那個屠殺我家人的改造人
The Augment who slaughtered my family.
他們稱她為”有印記的吉里”
They called her Giri the Morked.
她收留了我
She took me in.
讓我變得比常人更強大
Made me stronger than any human should be.
她把我撕碎
She ripped me opart
改造成她軍隊里的另一個改造人
and turned me into another Augment for her army.
我做了很多可怕的事
And I did terrible things.
都是為了像你這樣的魔頭
AlI for a monster like you.
因為對暴君來說 只有一個選擇
Because for tyrants, there is only one choice:
殺戮
murder.
你還沒有殺我
You haven't killed me.
暫時沒有
Yet.
我認出了那件武器 因為是我下令制造的
I recognized the weapon because I ordered it to be built.
召集你的人
Gather your people.
我們需要所有人手
We're gonna need every one of them.
在我的宇宙里 總有人在密謀
GEORGIOU: In my universe, there were always plotters.
總有政變
Always a coup.
所以我打造了一件武器來消滅所有威脅
So I built a weapon to end all threots.
我稱它為天賜
I called it the Godsend.
它會引發連鎖反應
It triggers a chain reaction,
像病毒一樣在行星間傳播
like a virus passing between planets.
所經之處 盡成灰燼
Everything in its poth incinerates.
整個象限都會毀滅
An entire quadrant would be lost.
如果我的敵人設法殺死我
If my enemies managed to kill me,
就再無統治的土地
there would be nothing left to rule.
呃 打擾一下 問個問題
ZEPH: Yeah, hi. Quick question.
抱歉
Sorry.
對 就是 呃 就一個小問題
Yeah, no. Uh, justαqu it's just a quick one.
是天賜還是天譴？
Is it Godsend or God's End?
天賜還是天譴？
Godsend or God's End?
我聽不出你說的有什麼區別
I don't hearα difference in what you're saying.
真的嗎？真的嗎？天賜 天譴
Really? Really? Godsend. God's End.
-我還是聽不出來 -天賜是…
Yeah, I'm still not getting it. - The Godsend is...
等等 天賜 我現在聽出來了
Wait, Godsend. I hear it now.
-是天賜 沒有譴字 -賜
lt's Godsend. No apostrophe. Send.
天賜就在這里
The Godsend is here.
怎麼可能？它來自另一個宇宙
How? lt's from another universe.
我不知道 但那個人有它
I don't know, but that man had it.
就是你認為是達達諾的人
The one that you think is Dada Noe.
我們知道他就是達達諾
The one we know is Dada Noe.
不 他不是你們的達達諾 不可能是
No, he's not your Dada Noe. He cqn't be.
他來自帝聯 而且帶來了天賜
He's from the Terran Empire, and he brought the Godsend here.
這是他知道天賜的唯一原因
That's the only way he can know about it.
既然我們已經把他關起來了
And since we have him locked up tight,
-我來審問他 -不 不 不
- I'II interrogate him. GARRETT: No, no, no.
-我們不能相信這個女人說的任何話 -對
We cannot trust a single word this woman says. Yeah.
她害死了梅勒
She cost us Melle.
她是唯一知道我們在對付什麼的人
She's the only one who knows what we're dealing with.
是啊 這是她說的 小弟
Yeah, well, so she says, little bro.
小？
Little? -
歧視我們小個子！
Scale- shamer!
微生物比恐龍活得久！
Microbes outlasted dinosaurs!
冷靜點 我是說…
Calm your boots. What I'm saying is...
我要尿你一身 讓你生銹！
I will piss in your suit until you go all rusty like!
...她才是搞砸一切的原因
...that she's the reason this is dll bollixed up.
梅勒死是因為她 我們在銀河系屁股眼
She's the reason Melle's dead, and she's the reason
也是因為她
we're in the ass end of the galaxy.
都聽著
ALOK: Listen up.
我和喬治歐要回船上去
Georgiou and I are gonna go back to the ship.
達達諾是我們找到天賜的唯一線索
Dada Noe is our only link to the Godsend,
所以我們要和他談談
so we're gonna have a little chat with him.
怎麼了？
What?
她是菲利帕·喬治歐
ALOK: Her name is Philippα Georgiou,
至高無上的帝國陛下
Her Most Imperial Majesty.
祖國之母
Mother of the Fatherland.
瓦肯的統治者
Overlord of Vulcan.
克林貢的主宰 安多星的女王
Dominus of Qo'noS, Reginα Andor,
菲利帕·喬治歐·奧古斯都·雅波尼烏斯·森塔利烏斯
Philippa Georgiou Augustus laponius Centarius.
厲害
DADA NOE: Cool.
還送薯條嗎？
That come with fries?
不錯吧？
: That was good, right?
好吧
Okay.
每次你不直接回答她的問題
ALOK: Every time you don't answer her questions directly,
陛下就會打你的臉
Her Majesty will punch you in your face.
好吧
: Fine.
我是達達
I'm Doda.
達達諾 就是達達 然後是諾
Dadα Noe. just Dada, then Noe.
就這樣 中間沒別的
That's it. No in- betweens.
然後我...
And l, uh.
我以前在瓦特殖民地管理一個病理實驗室
I used to run α pathology lab in the Watt Colonies.
搞什麼鬼啊？！
What the shit, man? !
你說她會打我臉的！
You said that she was gonna be doing the face punching!
現在我們都說謊了 你不是那個達達
So now we both have lied. You are not that Doda.
你是他們所說的鏡像
You're what these people call his Mirror.
你來自帝聯
You came here from the Terran Empire,
帶來了天賜
and you brought the Godsend.
什麼是天賜？
What's the Godsend?
我的戰爭委員會想要廢黜我
My own war council tried to depose me.
你知道我是怎麼讓元帥開口的嗎？
Do you know how I convinced the field marshal to talk?
嗯？
Hmm?
我是帝國武器設施
I was an administrator
的一名行政官員
αt an Imperial weapons facility on Terra.
嗯對
Uh, yeah.
天賜就存放在我的設施里
The Godsend was stored at my facility.
大多數人以為它只是個傳說 但我知道它是真的
Most thought it was a legend, but I knew it was real.
所以你想把它賣掉
So you tried to sell it.
對 對
DADA NOE: Yeah, yeah.
我想靠賣它的錢在這里安靜地生活
I wanted to Iive here quietly on its proceeds.
你是怎麼來到我們的宇宙的？
ALOK: How did you get to our universe?
嗯？
Hmm?
有一場離子風暴
There was an ion storm.
實際上是兩場
Two of them, actually.
當它們按規律匯聚時
And when they converged, which they do like clockwork,
在帝國邊緣撕開了什麼東西－
they ripped something open on the fringes of the Empire- -
他們稱之為異象 但其實是一條通道
αn anomaly, they called it- but it was a passageway
可以從帝聯到達這個地方
to get to this place from the Terran Empire.
它通向你們的新月星雲
Comes out through your Crescent Nebula.
知道的人很少 暫時是這樣
Few know obout it. For now.
但它四小時後會再次打開
But it'll open again in four hours.
那時我本該和買家見面
That's when I was supposed to be meeting my buyer.
你知道那武器會造成什麼後果嗎？
Are you aware of what that weapon does?
帝聯已經耗盡了資源
The Terran Empire's burned through its resources.
到處都是饑荒
There's famine.
整個生態系統都在崩潰
Entire ecologies are collapsing.
他們需要找到新的領地
They need to find a new territory
來征服和掠奪
to conquer and strip- mine.
當他們發現超級武器不見了
When they realize that their superweapon is gone,
他們就會找到那條通道
they're gonna find that passageway- -
你知道他們一定會的
you know they will and they'll come
他們會燒毀一切 奴役幸存者
αnd they'll burn everything they touch and enslave the rest,
陛下 這就是帝國的作風
because that's what the Empire does, Majesty.
他們都是跟你學的
: They learned well from you.
還有誰想要它
ALOK: Who else wants it?
我不知道 老兄
DADA NOE: I- I don't know, man.
我收到了報價 錢是真的
I got an offer. The money was real.
有人從我們這偷走了天賜武器
Someone stole the Godsend from us.
他是誰 不知道
- Who was he? - DADA NOE: No idea.
不管是誰闖入我的房間 偷走了武器
Whoever broke into my room, whoever stole that weapon,
他們之所以知道這些
they know what they know because they learned it
是從你們中的某個人那學來的
from one of you.
緊急傳送器
ALOK: Emergency transporter.
好吧 這很棒
Well, this is great.
哦 更妙了
Oh, even better.
那是…那是飛船嗎 飛船不見了嗎
ZEPH: Is that...is that the ship? Is the ship gone?
我喜歡那艘船
I liked that ship.
發生什麼事了
What hoppened?
破壞行動
Sabotage.
什麼
What?
偷走天賜武器的人有個幫手
GEORGIOU: Whoever stole the Godsend had a partner.
就在這里
lt was someone here.
這意味著我們中間有個內鬼
Which means one of us is a mole.
可能是你 也可能是你
Could be you. Could be you.
如果是我
GEORGIOU: If it were me,
你們早就都死了
I would have murdered all of you already.
老大 如果有內鬼 你知道不是我
Look, boss, if there's a mole, you know it's not me.
這話聽起來就像內鬼會說的
ZEPH: I meαn, that sounds pretty moley to me.
我不知道
- I don'tknow.
我們一起執行過十次任務了
QUASI: We've been on like ten ops together.
是啊 我連你長什麼樣都不知道
Yeah, andI still don't even know what you look like, do I?
沒人知道變形者的本來面目
No one knows what a Chameloid looks like.
你可以變成任何樣子 那弗茲呢
- You might change into anything you want. - What about Fuzz, huh?
他和我們完全不是一個量級的 轉移話題了
He exists on α whole other scale than anybody else. - Mm, deflecting?
我老婆快要產下我們的第一窩卵囊了
My wife is about to Iay our first litter of egg sacs.
不 我即將有19萬個幼崽 等等等等
No, Ihave190, 000 hatchlings on the way- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
我希望它們能活下來 聽著
...and I want them to live. Well, look,
你能給我們每個人都找到動機
you could find α motive for any of us.
也可能是我們中任意幾個人聯手
Or it could be a combination of any of you.
比如說澤夫和弗茲或者…
You know, like- like Zeph and- and Fuzz or...
沒有梅勒你就亂了分寸
You are spinning out without Melle.
你無法做出決定
You cannot land on a choice.
也許你說這話是因為你就是內鬼
Maybe you're putting that in my head because you're the mole.
嗯 加勒特怎麼樣 她是新人
Huh? How obout Garrett? She's new.
她根本不在意我們
She doesn't care obout us.
我是星際艦隊的人
I'm Starfleet.
哇 剛才有誰感覺到英雄氣息
Whoa. Anyone else feel that heroic breeze right there
吹動她的鬥篷了嗎
ruffling her cape?
好吧 那邊有艘舊船
GARRETT: Okαy, there's an old ship out there,
一艘廢棄的運輸船
αn old garbage scow.
是的 當你在上面
Yeah, Ifound it when you were up there
審問鐵頭的時候我發現的
interrogating metal head.
雖然多年沒人駕駛了
Must be years since anyone flew it,
但我覺得我們可以用它
but I think we can work with it
去追那個偷走天賜武器的人
to go after whoever took the Godsend.
嗯 我對你的厭惡減輕了
Mm. Idislike you less.
啊
Aw.
想讓人喜歡我 我會養條狗
If I wanted someone to like me, I'd get α dog.
我喜歡秩序
I like order.
我喜歡可預測性和結局
I like prediction and conclusion.
那你找錯隊伍了 因為我們這有內鬼
Then you're on the wrong team because we've got mole,
被困在一個死寂的星球上
stranded on a dead planet,
無法與外界聯系
no communication with the outside,
不到四小時泰倫人就能得到天賜武器
and less than four hours before the Terrans get the Godsend
他們可以在銀河系任何地方使用它
and use it anywhere in the galaxy.
說到這個奎斯 天線陣列怎麼樣
Speaking of which, Quas, what about the antenna array?
呃 這個…
Uh, well
它已經過時二十年了
Well, it's a couple decades out of date.
我們得讓它運轉起來 然後通知31部門即將發生的事
We get it up and running, then we tell 31 what's coming.
我們一起行動
We work together.
所有人都要保持在視線範圍內 好的
Everyone stoys in sight. - QUASI: Yeah.
就是…
just.
我們走吧
Let's go.
好吧 這個主意泡湯了
QUASI: Well, there goes that idea.
我們的小內鬼真是忙個不停
Our little mole has been really busy.
把所有線路都破壞了
Ripped up all the wiring.
分兩隊 我帶一隊進樹林
Two teams. I'll Iead one into the woods.
三個人去看看能否修好那艘破船
Three to see if we can salvage that scow.
你和其他人留在這
You stay here with the others
試著修覆天線陣列
αnd try and fix the antenna array.
她憑什麼現在給我們下命令
Why is she giving us orders now?
因為我允許她這麼做
Because I'm Ietting her
而且我很確定她不是內鬼
αnd l'm pretty certain she's not the mole.
你不會押注在一匹叫”很確定”的馬上
You wouldn't bet on a horse named Pretty Certain.
奎斯 弗茲 你們馬上和喬治歐去檢查那艘船
Quas, Fuzz, you get to the scow right away with Georgiou.
澤夫和加勒特留在這里和我一起
Zeph and Garrett, you stay here with me.
我們負責天線陣列
We'll take care of the antenna array.
呃 抱歉
Uh, I'm sorry.
我要和兩個想殺我的人
I'm supposed to go out into the woods
一起去樹林里
with two people who want to kill me?
保持在彼此視線範圍內 別死就行
Just stay in sight of each other and don't get dead.
好嗎
Okay?
好的 謝謝隊長
QUASI: Yep, thanks, Cap.
我是說 只有一半概率其中一個想殺我
I mean, just fifty- fifty shot one of them wants to kill me,
然後25%... 奎斯 趕緊滾出去
and then 25‰Quas, just get your ass out there.
我也愛你 隊長
Ilove you, too, Cop.
好了 遵命
ALOK: AII righty. QUASI: Aye, aye.
這艘破船的內部線路
QUASI: The internal circuitry on this old scow
狀況還算不錯
is still in decent shape.
我看到的部件都能用
Everything I'm seeing should work.
所以這個我們在追的東西 天賜武器
So this thing we're chasing, the Godsend,
你們的工程師有沒有裝保險裝置
your engineers, did they install a fail- safe?
我們能遠程禁用它嗎
Can we disable it remotely?
沒有失控保護 我不會允許這種東西
There is no fail- safe. I wouldn't allow it.
這很符合你的風格
How very on- brand for you.
我能再問一個問題嗎
Can I ask you one more question?
我就再問最後一個
I'mjust gonna ask you one more question.
你把神賜帶到這個世界上
So you brought the Godsend into the world
就為了消滅億萬生命
to vaporize quadrillions of lives.
從沒覺得這有點 你懂的 過分嗎
Never thought that was a little, you know, much?
我下令銷毀了它
I ordered it destroyed.
有人藏起來了 你的人背叛了你
And someone hid it. Your own people betrayed you.
你的企業文化爛透了
Well, your corporate culture was straight- up shit.
而且你還沒回答我的問題
And you didn't answer my question.
漸近線線圈不見了
The asymptote coil is gone.
有人一定是為了鋱把它拆走了
Someone must have scavenged it for the terbium.
找另一個這東西應該能飛
Well, find another one, this thing should fly.
-貨艙里可能有 -不行
Mαybe the cargo hull. Huh. Oh, no, no.
所有人要在一起 明白嗎
Everyone stays together, all right?
這樣你就沒機會殺我們了
Limits the possibilities of you killing us.
呃…
Uh.
我們去貨艙看看
Let's go to the cargo hold, please.
你不來嗎
Aren't you coming?
來 我可太期待了
Yes. Icouldn't be more excited.
我當然可以幫你
ZEPH: Yeah, Icould help you down there, of course,
但是考慮到你知道 控制欲
but considering how, you know, control
是你性格的核心
is central to your entire identity
而我又不擅長這個
αnd the fact that I'm just not good atit,
我就站在這里 尊重我們的關系
I'mjust gonna stand here and honor our relationship
-什麼都不做 -很有幫助
by doing absolutely nothing. ALOK: Helpful.
這叫徹底的自我接納
It's called radical self- acceptance.
-你很開明嘛 -謝謝
Evolved of you. Well, thank you.
你能修好嗎
So, can you fix it?
我都不確定它是不是壞了 只是缺了個零件
I'm not even sure it's broken. lt's just missing a part.
你看 這些斷裂的線路看著嚇人
Look, this- this torn wiring Iooks dramatic,
但這設備有備用系統
but this equipment has redundancy built in.
有簡單的替代方案
There's an easy work- around.
但theta接口被人扯掉了
Except somebody ripped out the thetq junction.
除此之外 這東西應該能用
Other than that, this thing should work.
那也許內鬼拿著它
Okay, well, maybe our mole has it.
-加勒特？ -嗯
Gαrrett? - Yeah.
澤夫
Zeph.
澤夫在哪
Where is Zeph?
澤夫 收到請回覆
Zeph, come in.
澤夫 聽到請回話
Zeph, do you copy?
澤夫
Zeph.
加勒特 是你弄的嗎
Garrett, was that you?
加勒特 那是什麼聲音
Garrett, what the hell was that?
有人啟動了天線陣列
GARRETT: Someone just αctivated the antenno array.
該死
Damn it.
發生什麼事了
What's happening?
加勒特 匯報情況
Garrett, sitrep.
這下有好戲看了
FUZZ: This is going to be good.
中尉 收到請回覆 完畢
ALOK: Lieutenant, do you copy? Over.
安全
QUASI: Clear.
GEORGIOU: Clear.
這里沒有
FUZZ: Nothing here.
怎麼可能有人用這個發送信號
How could someone have used this to send out α signal?
不可能 它缺了個零件
lmpossible. lt's missing a part.
而且被人打壞了
And someone shot it to hell.
我聽到有人在跑
GARRETT: I heard someone running.
澤夫一定是把theta接口裝回去了
Zeph must have put the thetq junction back in.
用完天線陣列後又打壞了它
Then shot it after he used the array.
他失蹤後一定是繞回來了
So he must hove circled back after he went AWOL.
澤夫來這個星球就是為了破壞我們的行動
Zeph came down to this planet to sabotage us.
現在我們被困在這里
And now that we're stranded,
他給他的同夥發了信息
he sent α message to whoever he's working with.
他會躲起來等援軍到了
And he'll lay low until his ride gets here,
然後就跑得無影無蹤
αnd then he's long gone.
那我們得先找到他
GEORGIOU: Then we need to find him first.
觀察手 收到請回覆
ALOK: Observer, do you copy?
突擊一號 我什麼時候沒收到過
GARRETT: Please, Raider One, when do I not copy?
有意思 情況如何
That's funny. Status?
這里幹擾很大
GARRETT: I'm picking up a lot of interference,
但三錄儀顯示澤夫的生命特征
but the tricorder shows Zeph's biosignature
剛剛出現在這個區域 完畢
was just in this sector. Over.
收到 保持隱蔽 跟緊點
Copy. Stay low and tight, people.
你效忠的軍閥吉里 她怎麼了
The warlord you served, Giri, what happened to her?
她死得跟活著一樣
She died like she lived.
你知道我什麼意思
By that, you know what I mean.
她很幸運
She was lucky.
沒被良心感染
She wasn't infected with a conscience.
-感染？-對
lnfected? - Yeah.
怪物就該是怪物
A monster can only be a monster.
有悔意的怪物毫無用處
A monster with regrets is useless.
所以你才躲在
Mm. So that's why you were hiding
那個鳥不生蛋的酒吧里
in α bar ot the ass end of nowhere.
也許這就是你為什麼要跟31部門合作
Maybe it's why you're working with 31.
為了洗清自己
To wipe your slate clean.
像我們這樣的人總要付出代價
ALOK: There's always α price to pay for people like us.
你在這里就說明你也同意
You wouldn't be here if you didn't agree.
原來你是這麼看我的
Oh, so that's why you chose me.
你覺得我是個有感情能被控制的怪物
You think I'm a monster who feels enough to be controlled
但還能幹臟活
but still do the real dirty work.
不我覺得你想要回神賜是因為你知道
No, I think you want the Godsend back because you know
這是你唯一的機會
it's your one chance to redeem yourself
彌補你的罪過
for all the shit you've done.
我要回神賜是因為它是我的
I want the Godsend bock because it's mine.
啊 澤夫的外骨骼在漏水
Ah. Zeph's exoskeleton is Ieaking.
對越來越多了
Yep, more.
這邊
GEORGIOU: This way.
布利普 克利普
Blip, Clip,
格利普
Grip,
小兒麻痹 流行感冒
Polio, lnfluensina,
-牛痘… -你在說什麼
- Cowpox...- What are you saying?
我在給我的孩子們起名字
I'm reciting the names of me hatchlings.
既然你們中有人要殺我
Since one of you is going to murder me,
我永遠見不到他們了 但至少我可以一一紀念他們
I'm never gonna meet them, but αt Ieast I can honor them
每一個
one by one.
崔普
Trip,
崔普2號
Trip 2,
扁桃體炎 克里米亞－剛果出血熱…
Tonsilyitis, Crimean Congo Hemorrhagic Fever...
你要把19萬個名字都哭訴出來嗎
Are you gonna sob out 190, 000 names?
你怎麼能這麼冷血無情
How can you be so cold and insensitive?
他可能記錄下發生的事了嗎
Might he have recorded what happened?
當然有
QUASI: Sure.
但影像可能和他一起消失了
Except the footage was probably murdered along with him.
我們可以把三錄儀連接到他的外骨骼上
ALOK: We could connect one of the tricorders to his suit.
只要還有數據 就能知道兇手是誰
Whatever data is left, we'll know who did this.
你這是在懷疑我們所有人
QUASI: You say that like we're all suspects.
我們不是 好嗎
We're not. All right?
福茲、我和她當時都在駁船上
Fuzz, me and her were in the scow when all this happened-
大家都在彼此的視線範圍內
everyone in sight of everyone else.
而且沒人離開過對吧
And nobody went anywhere, right?
-對 -嗯
Right. - GEORGIOU: Hmm.
這不是澤夫的
Oh, this is not Zeph's.
黑發25厘米
Brunette. 25 centimeters.
這太瘋狂了
This is insane.
別亂動
Stop fidgeting.
我和澤夫一起待了一周
I've been in close quarters with Zeph for a week.
好吧 你喜歡機械性愛
Okay, so you're into mecha boom- boom.
很多人類都這樣 沒什麼好羞恥的
Lots of humans are. No shame.
嗯
Hmm.
這不可能
Well, that's impossible.
加勒特中尉
ALOK: Lieutenant Garrett,
為什麼你的指甲下有澤夫的血
why is Zeph's blood underneath your fingernails?
加勒特中尉
GEORGIOU: Lieutenant Garrett,
在澤夫身上發現了你的痕跡
evidence from you was found on Zeph's body,
在你身上也發現了澤夫的痕跡
αnd evidence from Zeph's body was found on you.
一點都不星際艦隊
Not very Starfleet.
我非常星際艦隊
Oh, Iam very Starfleet.
你知道我沒做這事
And you know I didn't do this.
你只是害怕任何有道德準則的人
You are just terrified of anyone with a moral compass.
嗯
Mm.
在那顆純潔的心底
And deep down in that pure little heart,
你其實是個混亂小妖精 對吧
you're αctuallyα chaos goblin, aren't you?
-我知道你有這潛質 天使 -別這麼叫我
- I know you have itin you, angel. - Don't call me that.
星際艦隊看出了你的本質
Starfleet sniffed you out
把你安排在最有用的位置
αnd put you in a place where you'd be most useful.
31區正是那些懂得變通規則的軍官該去的地方
Section 31 is just the place for officers who bend the rules,
從不違規 直到他們違規的那一刻
never quite break them until they do.
你在這里很合適
And you fit right in here.
你隨便折磨我
GARRETT: You can torture me all you want.
你永遠不能把我變成殺人兇手
You will never make me o murderer.
不
ALOK: No.
找到錄像了！
QUASI: We've got footage!
住手！
ZEPH: Stop!
Stop!
這是我的外骨骼
This is my suit.
我就是外骨骼！
I am the suit!
外骨骼就是我！
The suit is me!
等一下
One second.
我們是朋友啊 我們是朋友
We were your friends. We were your friends.
你不能殺我
You can't kill me. -
-澤夫 不要 -你不能殺…
QUASI: Zeph, no. You can't kill...
澤夫是自殺的？
QUASI: Zeph killed himself?
他為什麼要這麼做
Why would he do that?
抱歉讓你失望了 陛下
Sorry to disappoint you, Your Majesty.
這一切都說不通
Look, none of this is making any sense.
對 一點都說不通
No, none of it makes a lick of sense.
他為什麼要這麼做 呃...
Why would he do this? Uh.
-給我幾分鐘... -我們沒時間了
Give me a couple minutes to......- We don't have minutes.
那給我幾秒鐘
QUASI: Well, then give me a couple seconds, then.
呃…
Uh.
-可能是你 -可能是你
Could be you. GEORGIOU: Could be you.
我甚至還不知道你長什麼樣
ZEPH: And I still don't even know what you look like.
你可以變成任何樣子
You could change into anything you want.
她是新來的她不在乎我們
QUASI: She's new. She doesn't care about us.
-我是星際艦隊的 -哇
I'm Starfleet. - Whoa.
說到外骨骼
ZEPH: When you are talking about the suit,
就是在說澤夫
you're talking about Zeph.
這不是福茲
FUZZ: This isn't Fuzz.
瓦肯人只是個機器 你知道的
The Vulcan's just a machine, you know.
我在里面
I'm inside.
歧視鱗片的人！
Scale- shamer!
你想不到我能鉆進多小的地方
You wouldn't believe the tiny spots I can get into.
比如 身體改造的內部構造
For example, the inner workings of body modifications.
有個自動駕駛
There's an autopilot.
這是唯一合理的解釋
That's the only thing that makes sense.
你把瓦肯機器設成了自動駕駛
You set the Vulcan machine on autopilot.
難怪它的反應那麼奇怪
That's why its responses were so strange.
-你不來嗎 -來了
Aren't you coming? - Yes.
你鉆進了澤夫的外骨骼
You flew into Zeph's exoskeleton.
一旦進去之後…
And once you were inside...
有人拆掉了西塔接頭
GARRETT: Somebody ripped out the theta junction.
加勒特 澤夫在哪
Garrett, where's Zeph?
然後你控制了澤夫的外骨骼
GEORGIOU: Then you took control of Zeph's suit.
當其他人出去找他的時候
While the others were out Iooking for him,
你讓他偷偷回到天線陣列
you made him sneak back into the antenna array
發送了那些信息
αnd send those messages.
別對他們下手！
Don't do this to them!
我們曾是朋友啊
We were your friends.
然後你就毀掉了證據
GEORGIOU: Then you destroyed the evidence.
還殺了澤夫
And you killed Zeph.
然後把證據栽贓給了加勒特
And then you planted the evidence on Garrett here.
舉起手來 費茲
Hands up, Fuzz.
真是見了鬼了
Oh, shite and ever shite.
你真要相信她說的話嗎 阿洛克？
Whoa. You're honestly gonna believe what she says, Alok?
奎斯 想想我們共同經歷的一切
Quasi, after everything we've been through?
我…我能先說一句話嗎？
C- Can Ijust say one thing first?
我還能控制澤夫的機甲
I'm still hacked into Zeph's exoskeleton.
快點！
GARRETT: Come on!
”絕不拋棄任何船員”呢？
What happened to"no crew member Ieft behind"?
哦
Oh.
快點 快點！
ALOK: Come on, come on!
靠近點
Get us closer.
我接住你了 我接住你了
QUASI: Igot you. Igot you.
該死
Nice and easy. ALOK: Damn.
你一直在關注黑市對吧？
You keep tabs on the black market, hmm?
在那里聽說了上天之眼
And that's where you heard about the Godsend.
你在意這個幹什麼？
Why do you care?
你殺了自己的家人
You killed your family.
再多幾十億人又算什麼？
What's a few billion more people, huh?
它在哪里？你在和誰合作？
Where is it? And who are you working with?
你就在他們身邊十步之遙
You took your crown while they died in agony
看著他們痛苦死去時奪取了王冠
not ten feet away.
你把唯一的朋友變成了奴隸
You condemned your only friend to slavery,
最後還厚顏無恥地對他施以仁慈？
and then you had the balls to offer him kindness at the end?
你怎麼會知道這些？
How could you know that?
終於明白了吧
Glad you're catching on.
他騙了你 陛下
He played you, Emperor.
桑還活著
San's alive.
這不可能
lt's not possible.
這怎麼可能？
That's not possible. How?
他一點點服用那種毒藥
He built up an immunity from that poison, you know.
慢慢建立起了抗體
Teeny tiny doses over time.
小人物又贏了一局 陛下
Once again, small shite for the win, mama.
他在哪里？！
Where is he? !
他會給你上一場好戲
He's gonna put on quite the show.
你制造了上天之眼
You built the Godsend.
這個怪物是你一手造就
You made this monster.
這都是你的錯
This is all you.
小心點 知道嗎？
Be careful, all right?
我說了小心點
I said be careful.
我還要靠這個活動呢
I have to get around in that.
你現在能買上百個這樣的了
SAN: You can afford α hundred of them now.
哦 太好了
FUZZ: Oh, great.
我只要一個能用的就行
I'd settle for one that works.
所以就是這個？
So that's it?
至高無上的上天之眼
The almighty Godsend.
等你當上皇帝後
When you're emperor,
最好給它換個不那麼讓人困惑的名字
maybe start by naming it something less confusing.
一旦通道打開
QUASI: Once that passageway opens up,
他就聯系地球人 他們就會過來
he contacts the Terrans, they come through.
他們會在這里引爆它
They're detonating it here.
他就成了帝國的寵兒
And he'd be the darling of the Empire.
他會把聯邦搞得一團混亂…
So he throws the Federotion into chaos.
星際艦隊會手忙腳亂
Starfleet will start scrambling.
正是入侵的好時機
Perfect time to invode.
你創造了這個東西
You gave birth to this thing.
我們做不到
- How do we stop it? - GEORGIOU: We don't.
我們被困在這里 追不上他
We're trapped here, so we can't follow him.
天線被毀了 警告不了任何人
The antenna's destroyed, so we can't warn anybody.
這都是借囗
That is bullshit.
我做不到
You can do better than that. - l can't.
上天之眼就是我
The Godsend is me.
我永遠都戰勝不了自己
I'm the only one I could never defeat.
過去總會追上你
The past always catches up with you.
對吧？
Right?
但不代表它總能贏
ALOK: Doesn't mean it always wins.
每個安全屋我都有後備計劃
Every safe house, I have a backup plan.
我們能讓那艘垃圾船啟動
We'll get that scow running.
老大 那垃圾船飛不起來
Boss, the scow won't fly.
沒有漸近線線圈不行
Not without an asymptote coil.
我們有一個
ALOK: We have one.
我們能追上桑
We'll catch up with San.
確保他聯系不上地球人
We'll make sure he can't contact the Terrans.
你拆了線圈
GARRETT: You ripped out the coil.
有內鬼在時不能告訴你們
Couldn't tell you while a mole was still running around.
混蛋
Asshole.
好了 奎斯 啟動它
Okay, Quas, give her a rip.
還是只有一個脈沖
Stil just one pulse.
搞定了
And we're in business.
好了團隊 我們只剩不到30分鐘了
Okay, team, we have less than 30 minutes.
奎斯 設定航向新月星雲
Quas, set a course for the Crescent Nebula.
這會很顛簸 很危險
AII right, this is gonna be bumpy and bad.
我猜桑的船上有武器吧
I'm assuming Sαn's ship will be armed.
是啊 地球人的船都有武器
Yeah, every Terran ship's armed.
他有質子炮 魚雷
He'll have proton cannons, torpedoes,
而我們只是艘垃圾船
αnd we are a garbage barge.
你笑什麼？
Why are you laughing?
因為情況不會更糟了
Because I can't imagine things getting much worse.
我們走
QUASI: Let's go.
這東西在牽引光束中間飛行
So, this thing flies around in the middle of a tractor field.
人們把垃圾丟進太空
People jettison their garbage into space,
垃圾船就在牽引光束里飛行
and the scow flies around and drags the trash
收集這些垃圾
αlong with the field.
一旦牽引光束裝滿了
Once the tractor field is full,
就把垃圾倒進星雲
it dumps the trash in the Nebula
讓輻射把它們分解掉
where it disintegrates in the rodiation.
我就說明這麼多
I just want to be clear.
你是說我們最好的武器就是
You're saying that our best potential weapon is
一個收集垃圾的光束？
α beam for collecting garbage?
-對 -太好了
Yes. Great.
嘿抱怨可解決不了問題
Hey, being judgy never helped anything.
-你去哪？-工程部
Where are you going? - Engineering.
既然這是我們唯一的武器
If that's our only weapon,
我要把所有能量都轉到牽引光束上
I'II redirect all power to the tractor beams.
這主意還不錯
That's actually a good plan.
我們就位了
FUZZ: We're in position.
通道馬上就會打開
The passagewoy will open soon.
你知道這一切結束後我想要什麼嗎？
Do you know what I want when this is all over?
就是一個大空間
Just α big space, you know,
讓我的幼蟲能隨意打洞和飛翔
for me hatchlings to tunnel and fly around and.
你想要什麼？
What do you want?
我要喬治歐在失敗中煎熬
I want Philippa Georgiou to marinate in her own defeat.
我知道你們是”永世宿敵
I get you guys are all"eternal nemesis,
性感又邪惡的糾葛”之類的 但是…
sexy evil tension"and stuff, but...
警報
SHIP COMPUTER: Alert.
發現來襲艦船
lncoming vessel.
檢測到碰撞軌道
Collision trajectory detected.
果然她把船弄起來了
Of course she got it off the ground.
我說我們該用魚雷
I say we should use the torpedoes.
他們發現我們了
QUASI: They've picked us up.
光子魚雷來襲
GARRETT: Photon torpedo incoming.
-還有五秒四… -現在真該躲開！
Impact in five, fourReally want to take evqsive action right now!
-三 二 一 -誇西保持航向 全力防護罩
...three, two, one. Quas, hold the course. Put everything in our shields.
她為什麼不改變航向？
Why isn't she changing course?
我又不是算命的
Do I look like a fortune teller?
牽引光束的能量夠用了嗎？
ALOK: Do we have enough juice to drag them with the tractor beam yet?
夠了 但我們承受不住再一次直接命中
Yeah, but we can't take another direct hit.
魚雷來襲 五 四…
Incoming torpedo in five, four...
-穩住 馬上就到了…… -三 二 一
Keep it steady. We're almost there...three, two, one.
就是現在
ALOK: Now.
警報 導航控制暫停
SHIP COMPUTER: Alert. Navigation control suspended.
他們想幹嘛 把我們拖垮？
What are they gonna do, drag us to death?
她想阻止我回到帝國
SAN: She's trying to stop me from reaching the Empire.
哦
Oh.
大家覺得這情況如何？
How's everybody feeling αbout this?
這是唯一的辦法
GEORGIOU: It's the only way.
這能成功
This can work.
輻射會削弱他們的防護罩
The radiation will wear down their shields.
是啊 問題是輻射也會影響到我們
Yeah, the thing is, the radiation hits us, too.
目標鎖定故障
SHIP COMPUTER: Target lock malfunction.
無法鎖定魚雷 炮塔離線
Ican't get torpedo lock. Cannons offline.
桑？
San?
桑
San.
桑！
: San!
輻射水平已達臨界值
SCOW COMPUTER: Rαdiation levels critical.
防護罩已失效 重覆 防護罩已失效！
Shields are down. I repeat, shields are down!
桑的呢？
And San's?
他的只剩12% 而且還在快速下降
His are at 12% and falling fast.
等離子體來襲！
QUASI: Plasma incoming!
要是挨上這樣一下
We get caught with a burst like that,
我們就完了
and we're done.
這太混亂了 加勒特
This is chaos, Garrett.
你知道你喜歡這樣 嗯？
You know you love it, hmm?
也許該接受它 跟它親熱一下
Mqybe let it in, make out with it a little.
這就是星際艦隊派你來這的原因
lt's why Starfleet put you here.
混亂就是我的炮友
Chaos is my friend with benefits.
對 加勒特 讓我們玩個痛快
Yeαh, Garrett, let's get messy.
-嗯？ -好啊
Hmm? - Okay.
-交給你了 誇西 -嗯
You got this, Quas. Uh- huh.
準備好了嗎？
You ready?
桑的防護罩只剩4%了
GARRETT: Sαn's shields are at four percent.
現在是2%
Two now.
他的防護罩失效了
His shields are down.
可以行動了
Good to go.
菲利帕！
SAN: Philippa!
這場較量只有
This contest only ends
一方死去才會結束！
when one of us is dead!
開始引爆程序
GODSEND COMPUTER: Detonation sequence activating.
你看 我們納米人不需要聯邦
See, the Nanokins, we don't need the Federation.
從來都不需要
We never have.
在你們這些巨獸發現我們之前 我們就是統治者
We ruled before you behemoths found us,
等你們消失後 我們還會繼續統治
αnd we will rule again after you're gone.
猜猜誰能在大爆炸中存活？
Guess who survives very Iarge explosions.
非常小的生物
Very small things.
現在失陪了 我要去切斷我們的船
Now, if you'll excuse me, I need to cut our ship loose.
抱歉如果你的朋友因此喪命
Sorry if your friends die in the process.
不 我開玩笑的
No, I'm joking.
我等不及要殺了他們
I can't wait to kill them.
再見了 你們這些大塊頭的廢物！
So long, you big lumps of shite!
誰在駕駛那艘船？
Who's flying that?
呃 根據傳感器顯示 只有一個微小的生命體
Uh, according to the sensors, one tiny life- form on board,
而且正朝我們飛來
αnd it's heading right for us.
鎖定導彈
Plot missile lock.
我們只有垃圾 對 就只有垃圾
We have trash, all right? Just trash.
只剩一個
BOTH: But one.
桑
YOUNG GEORGIOU: San.
等待生物特征信號確認
GODSEND COMPUTER: Awaiting biosignature confirmation.
我鎖定了法茲的穿梭機
I've got Fuzz's shuttle.
他正返回桑的船上
He's heading back to San's ship.
-我們勉強跟上了 -別跟丟他
We're barely keeping up. - Stay on him.
呃 我們沒有任何武器
Uh, we don't have any weapons.
我們有一船艙的垃圾
We have a payload bay full of trash.
別讓那艘穿梭機跑了
Do not lose that shuttle.
好的
Okay.
我什麼都不是
SAN: I was nothing!
那個男孩軟弱無能
That boy was soft, weak.
但在你的壓迫下 這些年讓我成長到今天
But all those years under your heel taught me who I am now.
帝國軍即將通過傳送門
The Empire's coming through that portal.
我的帝國
My Empire!
我們將以仁慈統治這個宇宙
And we will reign over this universe
不像你那樣殘暴
with righteous mercy, not like you!
沒有仁慈的獨裁者 聖
There are no benevolent dictators, San.
這是你教會我的
You taught me that.
我們還能挽回
We can come back from this.
重新開始
We can start over.
我愛混亂
GARRETT: Oh, Ilove chaos.
混亂才是我的菜
Chaos is my jam.
我愛混亂 我愛混亂
I love chaos. I love chaos.
加勒特 你在下面幹什麼
QUASI: Garrett, what the hell are you doing down there?
誇西 我可是受過訓練的星際艦隊軍官
Quasi, I am a trained Starfleet officer
我要活到當上艦長的那天
who fully intends on living long enough to be captain one day.
你得相信我 好嗎
You got to trust me, okay?
你好啊
ODD VOICE: Hi there.
真高興你找到我
I'm so glad you found me.
你剛說什麼
What'd you just say?
呃...呃…
GARRETT: Uh...uh...
這是個玩具
lt's αtoy.
看起來像是來自德羅姆星球的
Looks like it came from a Droom planet.
我們一起玩點有趣的吧
Shall we do something fun together?
哇 哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
你還好吧 星際艦隊
You okay down there, Starfleet?
哇
: Whoa.
來吧 來吧 來吧 來吧 好
Oh, come on, come on, come on, come on. Yes.
我們不讓德羅姆科技進入聯邦
Oh, we do not let Droom tech into the Federation
因為他們用特倫礦作為能源
because they use Terrenium as a power source.
你是要炸死我們對吧
Oh, you're gonna blow us up, aren't you?
最好祈禱這艘船的船體
You better hope that this ship's hull
是用托莫海特加固的
is reinforced with Tomohite.
我是個科學官
I am α science officer.
科學就是可控的混亂
And science is just controlled chaos.
混亂 混亂 混亂 混亂 混亂
Whoa, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos!
啊 快點
Ah, come on.
起來 你這笨機器人
Get up, you stupid robot.
不 不
No. No.
不
No!
待在費茲的船前面 這樣我們就能打開貨艙
Stay in front of Fuzz's ship so we can open the payload bay.
呃 對
Uh, yeah.
關於這個
About that.
誇西 馬上就要發生巨大爆炸了
Uh, thing is...Quasi, there's about to be α very large explosion.
這控制台用的是我不認識的語言
This console's in α language I don't know.
我能破譯一些
I can decipher some of it.
我只需要把它分解成詞素
I just have to break it down to morphemes
然後你知道的…巨大爆炸即將發生
αnd, you know...Large explosion impending.
這兩個按鈕任一個都可能打開貨艙
Either of these two buttons could open the cargo bay.
那就兩個都按
Okay, so push them both.
這兩個按鈕任一個也可能
Either of these two buttons could also
啟動自毀程序
initiate a self- destruct protocol.
反正我們都要爆炸了
- We're gonnα blow up anyway. - Uh- huh.
誇西 誇西 看著我
- Um, uh. Huh? - Quasi. Quasi, look at me.
你只需要做個決定
You just need to make o call.
你知道該怎麼做
You know what to do.
好吧 好
Okoy. Okay.
呃
Uh.
我們可以永遠做朋友
We can be friends forever...
想聽個有趣的事嗎
Do you want to hear something funny?
我在自動駕駛
I'm on autopilot.
見鬼了
What the hell?
我們都要死了
DROOM DOLL: We're all gonna die.
We're all gonna die.
不
No!
和你在一起真是太美好了
lt's wonderful just to be with you.
好耶
Whoo! - Whoa!
成功
Yes!
現在就死吧
Die now.
去告訴你的家人你變了多少
Go tell your family how much you've changed.
聖
San.
不 不
No. No.
不
No.
聖
San.
這不是我想要的
This is not what I want.
求你
Please.
我深愛著你
: llove you. : llove you.
聖
YOUNG GEORGIOU: San.
San.
對不起
I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你...你...你說得對
You- you- you were right.
我仍然需要你
I still needed you.
我一直需要…
I αlwoys needed.
讓你告訴我自己是誰即使到現在
To show me who I am, even now.
現在
Now.
我的…我的皇帝
M- M...My emperor.
我的愛
My love.
不
: No.
我們合而為一
We are one.
永遠
Forever.
離子風暴即將匯聚
SHIP COMPUTER: Ion storm convergence imminent.
通道正在開啟
Passageway is opening.
生物特征信號確認
GODSEND COMPUTER: Biosignature confirmed.
60秒後引爆
Detonation in 60 seconds.
電腦 鎖定通道
GEORGIOU: Computer, target lock on the passogeway.
目標鎖定確認
SHIP COMPUTER: Target lock confirmed.
如果能回到過去
GEORGIOU: If you could go back,
當你跪在吉里面前時
αnd you were kneeling in front of Giri,
你會殺了她嗎
would you kill her?
你願意終結所有的痛苦和煙霧
Would you put a stop to all the suffering and smoke forever,
即使這意味著你必須死去
even if it meant that you had to die?
會
Yes.
很高興認識你 阿洛克·薩哈爾
Then I'm glad I knew you, Alok Sahar.
30秒後引爆
GODSENDCOMPUTER: Detonation in 30 seconds.
通道已開啟
SHIP COMPUTER: Passageway is open.
傳感器顯示他們啟動了脈沖引擎
QUASI: Sensors show they've activated impulse engines.
什麼
What?
-快把他們傳送回來 -好
Yeah. You need to transport them back.
-快 -馬上
Yeah. Okay. GARRETT: Now.
好的好的好的好的
QUASI: Okay, okay, okoy, okay.
風暴幹擾太強 我無法鎖定他們
The storm's interfering. I can't lock on to them.
10秒後引爆
GODSEND COMPUTER: Detonation in ten seconds.
來啊 快啊
QUASI: Come on. Come on!
他們快沒時間了
GARRETT: They're running out of time.
我在努力
QUASI: I'm trying.
5秒後引爆
GODSEND COMPUTER: Detonation in five,
4 3
four, three,
two, one.
加勒特中尉
GEORGIOU: Lieutenant Gorrett?
瑞秋
Rachel?
你沒事吧
You all right?
-我沒事 -嗯 你在這兒
- l'mokay. Hmm? You here?
-是的 你還活著 -好的
Yeah. You're αlive. All right.
對 奎西救了我們
Yeah, Quasi got us out.
-太好了 -謝謝
There we go. There we are. - GEORGIOU: Thank you.
你做到了
GARRETT: Oh, you did it.
我們贏了
: Oh, we won.
噢 成熟點
GEORGIOU: Oh. Grow up.
過度興奮真讓人惡心
Perkiness is disgusting.
是啊
Yeah.
我懂你
I hear you.
開始了
lt's happening.
通道正在崩塌
The passageway's collapsing.
她來了
There she is.
匯報情況如何
How was your debrief?
還行 不算太糟
Oh, could've been worse.
他們給了我一個提議
They made me an offer.
然後呢
And?
我還在考慮
l'm sitting on it. -
你呢
You?
呵 嗯
Meh. Hmm.
嗯
Hmm.
你以為這樣能瞞我
And how long did you think
多久呢 嗯
you could fool me with this, hmm?
-什麼露餡了 -嗯
- What gave it away? - Mm.
你看著我時還是會緊張
You still get nervous when I look at you.
呵 你好 船長
Oh. Hey, C- Cap.
別難為那個可憐人了
ALOK: Leave that poor man alone.
維吉爾
Virgil.
給我的朋友們來一輪仙釀
A round of elixirs for my friends.
-榮幸之至 杜弗朗克夫人 -嗯
Pleasure, Madame du Franc. Mm- hmm.
加勒特中尉
Lieutenant Gorrett.
他們讓你離船了
They let you off the ship.
現在是加勒特中校了
lt's actually Lieutenant Commander Garrett now.
-噢 -非常感謝
Oh. - Thank you very much.
如果這個小隊要成為常駐編制
And if this unit is gonna be a permanent detail,
那你們肯定需要監管
then you all definitely need oversight.
我隨時可能把你們都殺了
I may slaughter you all at any moment.
這算個問題嗎
Is that αdeal- breaker?
-不算 -無所謂
Nah. Whatevs.
反正你也不需要理由
It's not like you need a reason anyway.
說得對 你就是個狠人
- lt's true. You'reαbad bitch. -
-眼神都能殺人 -噢 我們懂
With the stare of death. QUASI: Oh, we get it.
你就是個可怕的無情殺手
You're a terrifying, soulless murderer
我們永遠無法信任你
who we can never truly trust.
我愛死這樣了
I love that for us.
總要有人讓生活有點樂子
Somebody's got to keep things lively.
-說得好 -對 說得好 -有道理
QUASI: Touche. - ALOK: Yes, touche. You make a point.
為我們幹杯
To us.
這不會是毒藥吧
This isn't poison, is it?
既然我們都在這兒了
GEORGIOU: And now that you have us all here,
接下來呢
what next?
還不是全部
Well, not quite all.
女士們先生們 看左邊
Ladies and gent, stage left.
你在開玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
我不是福茲
: Oh, I'm not Fuzz.
31區在黑市上買了
Section 31 bought
兩個這樣的運輸器
two of these conveyances on the black market.
我叫薇思 是他的妻子
Name's Wisp. I'm his wife.
等我們追上那個
And I'm here for when we catch up with
背信棄義的混蛋時就知道了
that lying, double- dealing son of a bitch.
呃 我們炸了他的船 女士
Uh, well, we blew up his ship, ma'am.
-呃 福茲夫人 -噢 親愛的
- Uh, Mrs. Fuzz. Oh, honey.
大爆炸中有時也會有小東西存活
Little things sometimes survive big explosions.
等找到他 我有話要問他
And when we find him, I have questions.
-說起這個 -正等你問呢
- Now, what are we talking αbout? - ALOK: I'm glad you asked.
我正要告訴團隊
I was just letting the team know.
指揮部給我們安排了任務
Control has a job for us.
我的理智這兩天
My better judgment has been
一直在對我大喊
screaming at me for two days now.
說你們這些人會害我丟掉工作
It keeps saying that you lot are gonna cost me my job.
-有可能 -她說不定會
- We might. - She might.
我讓理智閉嘴
CONTROL: I told my judgment to shut up
去睡覺
αnd tqke a nap.
因為我們有活要幹
Cause we have work to do.
有人去過圖爾卡納四號嗎
Hqs anybody been to Turkana IV?
-呼 -等等
- Whew. QUASI: Wait.
你說圖爾卡納還是朱爾納納
Did you say Turkana or say jur- jurnana?
他以為是”你媽媽四號”
He thought"Your Mama IV. "
噢 你媽媽四號
: Oh, Your Mamα IV.
不是
GEORGIOU: No. -